

# Arnulfo Israel Ramos Magaña

**Full Stack Developer** 

#### **Contact Information**

Email: arnulfo\_israel@hotmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/israel-

GitHub: https://israelramosm.github.io/ ramos/

Phone: 3411362414

#### **Profile**

I worked in different technologies and projects, and I like to use different kinds of languages and frameworks. Also, I worked on C# and .NET framework; I also work on Angular projects and java. Now my expertise is focused on full stack projects using Express, React/Redux and Svelte, with the use of IBM Cloud technologies and learning new ones like Nestjs.

#### **Technical Skills**

## **Technologies**

- HTML5
- CSS
- Javascript
- React/Redux
- Node
- Expressjs
- REST
- Git

- Bootstrap
- JQuery
- C#
- .NET Core
- ASP.NET
- Java
- Webpack
- AngularJS
- TypeScript

#### Certifications

- App Builder, Microsoft Certified Professional
- Web Applications, Microsoft Certified Professional

## **Work Experience**

## IBM – Full Stack Developer

#### Feb 2019 – Today

- Working on a new project using IBM cloud technologies like IBM event streams (Kafka) and databases. Svelte as fronted and nestjs as backend.
- Worked on a project using svelte as fronted and express as backed, also I implemented a functionality to send confirmation emails.
- Worked on internal project using React/Redux for the fronted and express for the backend, with a connection to IBM cloud technologies and database.

## Tata Consuntancy Services – Developer

#### Feb 2019 - Oct 2020

- Worked on a backend project using java
- Involved in internal projects
- Worked with Learning and Development team to organize and give sessions about the technologies and tools that we constantly use in the workspace

### **Unosquare – Software Engineer**

## Mar 2017 - Ago 2018

- Made a static website using HTML5, JS, CSS3, jQuery, bootstrap and .NET with C#
- Worked on several opened source projects using frameworks like angular, Typescript, React and configurations with webpack, I also did unit testing
- Used C# with .NET and .NET Core, usually making modifications that required changes to the API and connection to a Database. I also did unit testing.

# Unosquare – Internship

Sep 2016 – Mar 2017

• Was preparing and passed the certification test form Microsoft 480, 486 and 487.

## **Education**

#### **Guadalajara University – Telematics Enginner**

Jan 2013 - Dec 2016

Cisco Networking Academy

# Languages

Spanish – Mother Tongue English - Intermediate